zootemplate.com 2019-01-28

# Privacy Policy - ZooTemplate

### 1\. Introduction

ZooTemplate is the ultimate name to compute with commitment and protection of our valued customers privacy. Your privacy is essentially important to us and we consider it as one of the most vital elements of our business and it´s success. The purpose of this Website Privacy Policy is to outline how we deal with any personal data you provide to us while visiting this web site. Naturally, if you are not happy with this Website Privacy Policy you should not use this website.

By visiting this website, you are accepting the terms of this Website Privacy Policy. Any external links to other web sites are clearly identifiable as such, and we are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of these other websites.

### 2\. Types of Information Collected

We retain two types of information:

#### Personal Data

This is data that identifies you or can be used to identify or contact you and may include your name, address, email address, user IP addresses in circumstances where they have not been deleted, clipped or anonymised, and telephone number. Such information is only collected from you if you voluntarily submit it to us.

#### Non-Personal Data

Like most websites, we gather statistical and other analytical information collected on an aggregate basis of all visitors to our website. This Non-Personal Data comprises information that cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as demographic information regarding, for example, user IP addresses where they have been clipped or anonymised, browser types and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of our website.

### 3\. Purposes for which we hold your Information

#### Non-Personal Data

We use the Non-Personal Data gathered from visitors to our website in an aggregate form to get a better understanding of where our visitors come from and to help us better design and organize our website.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We don’t use cookies. However, Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, We have no access to or control over these cookies, once We have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

#### Personal Data

We will process any Personal Data you provide to us for the following purposes:

  1. to provide you with information you have requested;
  2. to contact you if required in connection with your query or to respond to any communications you might send to us;
  3. to send you the ZooTemplate Newsletter or Event Alerts.

### 4\. Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

We may provide Non-Personal Data to third parties, where such information is combined with similar information of other users of our website. For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of unique users who visit our website, the demographic breakdown of our community users of our website, or the activities that visitors to our website engage in while on our website. The third parties to whom we may provide this information may include potential or actual advertisers, providers of advertising services (including website tracking services), commercial partners, sponsors, licensees, researchers and other similar parties.

We will not disclose your Personal Data to third parties unless you have consented to this disclosure or unless the third party is required to fullfil your order (in such circumstances, the third party is bound by similar data protection requirements. We will disclose your Personal Data if we believe in good faith that we are required to disclose it in order to comply with any applicable law, a summons, a search warrant, a court or regulatory order, or other statutory requirement.

### 5\. Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### 6\. YOUR DATA PROTECTION RIGHTS UNDER THE GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (GDPR)

  * If you wish to **access, correct, update, or request deletion** of your personal information, you can do so at any time by contact us.
  * In addition, you can **object to the processing** of your personal information, ask us to **restrict the processing** of your personal information, or **request portability** of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by contact us.
  * You have the right to **opt-out of marketing communications** we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “opt-out” link in the marketing emails we send you. To opt-out of other forms of marketing, please contact us by contact us.
  * Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can **withdraw your consent** at any time.  Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
  * You have the **right to complain to a data protection authority** about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority.

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

### 7\. How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please don’t hesitate to contact us!

### 8\. Changes to the Website Privacy Policy

Any changes to this Website Privacy Policy will be posted on this website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any time we decide to use Personal Data in a manner significantly different from that stated in this Website Privacy Policy, or otherwise disclosed to you at the time it was collected, we will notify you by email, and you will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in the new manner.
